export const quizSubject = "PT1 - NUMB - GEOM & Measure & ALGEBRA";

let questions = [
  {
    "numb": 1,
    "question": "Calculate 3/4 + 1/5.",
    "answer": "19/20",
    "options": [
      "4/9",
      "15/20",
      "19/20",
      "17/20"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 2,
    "question": "Simplify (x^3)^2 * x^4.",
    "answer": "x^10",
    "options": [
      "x^9",
      "x^10",
      "x^14",
      "x^24"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 3,
    "question": "A trapezium has parallel sides of length 8 cm and 12 cm, and a perpendicular height of 5 cm. Calculate its area.",
    "answer": "50 cm^2",
    "options": [
      "40 cm^2",
      "60 cm^2",
      "50 cm^2",
      "100 cm^2"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 4,
    "question": "Solve the equation 3x - 7 = 8.",
    "answer": "x = 5",
    "options": [
      "x = 1/3",
      "x = 5",
      "x = 1",
      "x = 15"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 5,
    "question": "A rectangular prism has a length of 10 cm, a width of 4 cm, and a height of 3 cm. What is its volume?",
    "answer": "120 cm^3",
    "options": [
      "17 cm^3",
      "40 cm^3",
      "120 cm^3",
      "170 cm^3"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 6,
    "question": "Simplify (2x^3)^2.",
    "answer": "4x^6",
    "options": [
      "2x^6",
      "4x^5",
      "4x^6",
      "2x^5"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 7,
    "question": "Calculate the area of a circle with a radius of 5 cm. Use Ï€ = 3.14.",
    "answer": "78.5 cm^2",
    "options": [
      "31.4 cm^2",
      "78.5 cm^2",
      "15.7 cm^2",
      "100 cm^2"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 8,
    "question": "Solve the equation: 3x - 7 = 11.",
    "answer": "x = 6",
    "options": [
      "x = 4",
      "x = 2",
      "x = 6",
      "x = 18"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 9,
    "question": "Express 0.0000045 in standard form.",
    "answer": "4.5 x 10^-6",
    "options": [
      "4.5 x 10^6",
      "45 x 10^-7",
      "0.45 x 10^-5",
      "4.5 x 10^-6"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 10,
    "question": "A rectangular prism has a length of 6 cm, a width of 4 cm, and a height of 3 cm. What is its volume?",
    "answer": "72 cm^3",
    "options": [
      "13 cm^3",
      "24 cm^3",
      "48 cm^3",
      "72 cm^3"
    ]
  }
];

export { questions };
